Guide to the Business Office, Yale School of Drama, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of the Business Office, 1983-1987; Accession 1989-A-027
  - 1986-1987
    - Park Plaza, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Paul's Wire Rope, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Petty Cash, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 393)
    - Polyline Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 394)
    - Postage, Bulk Mail, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 395)
    - Postage, Business Reply Mail, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 396)
    - Presto, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 397)
    - Production Arts, Inc., 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 398)
    - R (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - Request for Services, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Russell Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 408)
    - S (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 409)
    - Sales Tax Report-YRT, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Sager Electric, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Senco Fastening, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Seton Name Plate Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Simon and Kumin, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Slocum and Sons, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - S.N.E.T. Co., 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Sosenky ' s, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - SSDandC, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Stage Lighting Rental, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Star Distributors, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Stephen Dunn and Associates, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - T (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Telephone Service Requests, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - TCG, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Theatre Crafts Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Theatre Magic, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Theatre Techniques, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Ticket Craft, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 435)
    - Touche International Products, Ltd., 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 437)
    - Towers Pharmacy, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 438)
    - Tyco, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 439)
    - U (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 440)
    - V (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 441)
    - W (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 442)
    - West Haven Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 443)
    - West Haven Lumber, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 444)
    - Western Costume, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 445)
    - Y (general), 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 447)
    - Yale Computer Center, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 448)
    - Yale Daily News, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 449)
    - Yale Lock Shop, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 450)
    - Yale Physical Plant, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 451)
    - Yale Printing Service, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 452)
    - York Chevron, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 453)
  - Old Actors' Files, 1983
    - A, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 454 - 457)
    - B, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 458 - 462)
    - C, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 463 - 494)
    - D, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 495 - 513)
    - E, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 514 - 518)
    - F, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 519 - 526)
    - G, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 527 - 549)
    - H, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 550 - 567)
    - I, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 568 - 569)
    - J, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 570 - 577)
    - K, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 578 - 593)
    - L, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 594 - 614)
    - M, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 615 - 641)
    - N, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 642 - 652)
    - O, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 653 - 660)
    - P, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 661 - 681)
    - R, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 682 - 703)
    - S, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 704 - 733)
    - T, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 734 - 738)
    - V, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 739 - 742)
    - W, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 743 - 762)
    - Y, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 763)
    - Z, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 764 - 765)
- Personnel files, 1993-2000; Accession 2005-A-032
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2076
  - 1993: (Box 1)
  - 1995:
  - 1996:
  - 1997:
  - 1998:
  - 1999:
  - 2000:
  - JOB SEARCH FILES FY 1999-2002
    - FY1999:
      - Sound Supervisor I (Box 2)
      - Fight Coach (Box 2)
    - FY2000:
      - Marketing Director/Asst. Prof. Adj (Box 2)
      - Sound Supervisor (Box 2)
      - Operations Assistant (Box 2)
    - FY2001:
      - First Hand (Box 2)
      - Dean's Assistant (Box 2)
      - Business Office Assistant (Box 2)
      - Marketing Manager (Box 2)
      - Shop Carpenter (Box 2)
      - New Audience and Groups Manager (Box 2)
      - Sound Technician/Designer (Box 2)
    - FY2002:
      - Marketing Associate (Box 2)
      - Asst. Prof. Adj/Marketing and Communications Director (Box 2)
      - Media Relations Manager (Box 2)
      - Operations Coordinator (Box 2)
      - Shop Carpenter (Box 2)
  - Employee Tax Paperwork, 1992-2000 (Box 3)